(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
検索した人
The person who searched
「#SSholoX4周年」を検索した人間に降りかかる
The person who searched '#SSholoX4thAnniversary'...
数々の出来事――
...many incidents will befall them.
ルイ姉……
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから……
Iroha, it's okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
ばぁ！
Baa!
終始鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー
I was getting goosebumps the whole time!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
HoloX 4th Anniversary is the best!
Six...
Let's go!
ラララパッタ　パラララパッタ...
La la la patta, pa ra la la patta...
迷宮なラビリンス / 作詞・作曲・編曲：ハヤシトモノリ
Labyrinthine Labyrinth / Lyrics, Comp, Arr: Tomonori Hayashi
迷宮なラビリンス
Labyrinthine Labyrinth
No Money かれた招待状
No money, a withered invitation
『秘密で秘匿の異次元マンションへ！』
"To a secret, hidden, interdimensional apartment!"
ガタガタのドアの笑声に
To the laughter behind the rattling door,
No Pain, No Gain アンチェイン！
No Pain, No Gain, unchain!
Get off my horse eye
迫る僕らは Walk Cry
Closing in on us, a walk cry
本能的に突破口も
Instinctively, even the breakthrough
堂々巡りの走馬灯
Is a revolving lantern of circular logic
迷宮に囚り込まれてゆくわ
Getting lured into the labyrinth
革命的に飾れ
Adorn it revolutionarily
不条理めく見学ツアー
The absurd observation tour
どわっはっはと愛を注入
Injecting love with a big 'Dwahaha!'
さあ、沸き起こせ 宵々ピューワー
Come, rouse the late-night purer feelings
響き合え 笑い声
Resonate together, voices of laughter
因果応報
Retribution
力こそパワー
Might is power
素敵な迷宮なラビリンス
The lovely Labyrinthine Labyrinth
迷える子羊君たち
You lost little lambs
お砂糖スパイス　それとピンクな4周年で
With sugar, spice, and a pink 4th anniversary,
ハイになれるドリンクできたよ
I've made a drink that'll get you high.
毒も飲んでくださいね
Please drink the poison too.
ホロックス酒に
To HoloX liquor!
さあさあ、皆々様、飲めや歌えや
Come now, everyone, drink and sing!
我輩もだ！
Me too!
いや、お前が飲むんかい
Wait, you're the one drinking it?!
じゃあ、とりあえず
Well then, for now...
乾杯！
Cheers!
黄泉の回廊から
From the corridor of Hades
帝王の礼装警報
Emperor's formal wear alarm
塗り替えられる宵や
The night that gets repainted
見果てぬ 笑い声
Undying voices of laughter
お前たちもな！
You too!
立ち止まれ 五人の鼓動
Stop, the heartbeats of five...
重ねて 声を高らかに
overlapping, voices raised high!
ラパパ ダララパパ
Ra-pa-pa, da-ra-ra-pa-pa
天辺の 海を越えるため
To cross the sea at the summit.
つまり本件 力こそパワー的な
In short, this case, power is power-esque,
迷宮な
a labyrinthine...
スーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
Super Future Party Labyrinth!
ホロックス！
holoX!
うわああああ！
Whooooooo!
ということで！
And so!
ホロックス、四周年！
holoX's 4th Anniversary!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations! Happy Anniversary!
よーしみんな、張り切っていくぞー！
Alright everyone, let's give it our all!
じゃあちょっとね これからの活動の抱負を...
Well then, let's share our resolutions for the future...
早いね展開 早いね
That was quick! Moving right along.
私から？私から？
From me? From me?
聞いてないよー どうしようかな
I wasn't ready! What should I do?
えっと、みんな、ありがとう！
Um, thank you, everyone!
五年目も頑張るぞ！ホロックス頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best in the 5th year! holoX will do its best!
イェーイ！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
はい、じゃあこよりちゃん！
Okay, next, Koyori-chan!
はい！えー、この五年目は四人でもっと
Yes! Um, in this 5th year, the four of us will...
団結力をガッと強めて
strengthen our bond significantly,
そろそろ日本征服ぐらいはしていきたいなと
and I want to finally achieve Japan Domination.
確かに 確かに
True, true.
五年目っていう いい区切りのところでね
At the good milestone of the 5th year.
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど
The world might still be a bit tough, but...
日本征服頑張ります！
I'll do my best for Japan Domination!
はい、いろは氏！
Okay, Iroha-shi!
はい！皆さん！ご、ご、ござるのごー！
Yes! Everyone! Go, go, Go of Gozaru!
五年目も元気に健やかに健康に活動頑張ります！
I'll keep working healthily and energetically in the 5th year!
ホロックス五年目頑張るぞー！
holoX 5th year, let's do our best!
五周年まで頑張ろう また
Let's work hard until the 5th anniversary!
はい、じゃあ私いいですか？
Okay, can I go next?
今年も、生き残るぞー！
I'll survive this year too!
毎年同じこと言ってるよね
You say that every year.
でも生き残れた 今年も
But I survived this year too!
そして、来年こそ
And starting next year...
五年目こそ 我々の年にするぞ！
the 5th year will be our year!
うわあああああ！
Whooooooo!
ちょっとダサい 待ってダサい
That's a bit lame... wait, it's lame.
なんでなんで？同じことやってんじゃん
Why? You're doing the same thing!
こよりのダサさはどうでもいいです
Koyori's lameness doesn't matter.
はい、ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ
Okay, everyone, please take a look.
ライブステージ！
The live stage!
すごーい！ めっちゃかっこよくない？
Amazing! Hasn't it become super cool?
ホロックスの最新ステージ！
holoX's newest stage!
最初のさ 登場からさ うちらかっこよかったでしょ？
From the opening, we were cool, right?
かっこよかったっしょ！
We definitely were!
待って待って ホロックスのロゴに助けられちゃったからね
Wait, we were helped by the holoX logo.
しかも このステージ ただ広いだけじゃなくて
And this stage isn't just wide,
色んな仕掛けがありますので
it has various gimmicks.
注目して なんかね 出てきたりとか
Keep an eye out, things might come out.
出てきたり 出てきたり
Coming out, coming out...
耳入る？
Do ears go in?
耳はもう入ってる
Ears are already in.
そして 上がったりとか
And going up!
尻尾 尻尾が上がってんぞ
The tail, the tail is going up!
変形したりとかさ 合体とか
Like transforming or combining...
合体！合体したい！
Combining! I want to combine!
できますか？こよりさん
Can we do it, Koyori-san?
合体はやりたかったんですけど...
I wanted to do the combination, but...
さすがにホロックス 予算が少なく...
unfortunately, holoX's budget is a bit low...
当たり前じゃない！ こよりさんいくらかけてると思ってるんですか
Of course it is! How much do you think we're spending?
五人の給料もっと上げてくれてもいいよね
They could raise our salaries for the five of us.
ウェーイ！でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん
But this stage was built, so it's fine.
ありがとうこより！
Thank you, Koyori!
ということで 五年目もホロックスの皆さん
And so, everyone in holoX, in the 5th year too...
こんな我々ですけど よろしくお願いします！
though we're like this, please treat us well!
ちなみに ここでお知らせでございます
By the way, we have an announcement here.
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると
If you join the Hololive official channel membership,
限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになります！
you'll be able to use exclusive emoji stamps!
ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
Please use them in the comments and liven things up!
さらに！今日からもう一つ メンバーシップ特典があるらしく
Furthermore! There's another membership perk starting today.
新曲「スキデカ」と「プライベートアイズ」の
Wallpapers for our new songs, "Sukideka"
壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
and "Private Eyes" are also available!
俺たちが欲しい！
We want them!
俺たちも入らなきゃいけないのか
Do we have to join too?
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、そして本日は何やらライブだけではなく...
Yes, and today it's not just a live performance...
おっ？ 重要な？ えっ、重要？
Oh? Important? Wait, important?
情報が盛り盛り盛りだくさんらしいので
It seems there's a lot, lot, lots of important information!
盛り盛り盛りだくさん！
Lots, lot, lots of it!
マジで！？
Seriously!?
盛りだくさん！
Lots!
みなさん、最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
Everyone, make sure to watch until the very end!
途中離脱禁止です！よろしくお願いします！
Leaving halfway is prohibited! Please look forward to it!
盛り盛り盛りだくさん、森の字を作って...
Lots and lots, making the shape of the 'Mori' character...
やめろ！ 何してんの？
Stop it! What are you doing?
3人で混ぜるな！混ぜるな！
Don't mix the three of us! Don't mix us!
ちょっと待ってください、何ですかこれ？
Wait a second, what is this?
早くしないと！
We have to hurry!
うん、みんなに見せらんないから、ライブ！
Yeah, we can't show everyone the live otherwise!
たしかに！
True!
はい、早速、最初は...！
Alright, starting off, first is...!
はい！こよちゃんのパートから！
Yes! Starting with Koyori-chan's part!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なん、何だそのポーズｗ
Wh-What's with that pose? lol
絶妙に見てくださいｗ
Please look closely. lol
可愛いか？ カエルか？
Is it cute? Is it a frog?
ちょっとちょっとｗ あ、可愛いね！
Wait, wait... Oh, it's cute!
こよちゃんいってらっしゃい！
Have a good performance, Koyori-chan!
バイバーイ！見ててね！
Bye-bye! Watch me!
見てるよー！ 頑張れー！
We're watching! Good luck!
走って！ほら、そこ広いから！
Run! Look, it's spacious over there!
急かさないでー！
Don't rush me!
あ、邪魔だから行くよｗ
Ah, we're in the way, let's go.
えっ、俺たちも？ おっとっと...
Eh, us too? Whoops...
ほら早く、早く、遅い、遅い！
Come on, hurry, hurry, you're slow, slow!
行くぜ、行くぜ、早く！
Let's go, let's go, hurry!
爆ラヴ＋ケミストリー
作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
Baku Love + Chemistry
Lyrics/Comp/Arr: NayutalieN
ラブは不安定 存在自体マジ感
Love is unstable, its very existence feels like magic
調合は未完成 トキメキのケミカル
The mixture is incomplete, a chemical of excitement
ふむなるほど そんじゃこれならどうだ
Hmm, I see. Then how about this?
混合ポーション ラブラブに！
Mixing the potion, into Love-Love!
解！合わさる 魔法のポーション
Solve! The magic potion that mixes together
混ぜるほどに甘くなるなる
The more you mix, the sweeter it gets
会！チュー！ 感情のモーション
Hi! Chu! The motion of emotions
奇跡的に美味しくなあれ
Become miraculously delicious
フラスコにハート やべ、出たアト
Heart in the flask, oh no, it came out afterwards
合格のテスト 君が一番
Passing test, you're number one
ほら僕は君になれ
Look, I can become you
ちょっと危険な まぜまぜ
A slightly dangerous mix-mix
爆弾！ケミストリーダンス
Bomb! Chemistry dance
曖昧な君狂わすグラフィ
A graph that drives the ambiguous you crazy
平和な恋のジェネリック
Generic of a peaceful love
もっと夢中になれなれ
Become more and more obsessed
最！低！僕を食べて
Worst! Best! Eat me
キュンさせて留めたい君の胸
I want to make your heart throb and stay there
今まさに 幸福のラッシュ
Right now, a rush of happiness
爆弾！君とケミストリー
Bomb! Chemistry with you
猛毒の甘いエージェント
Highly toxic sweet agent
溶けるくらいドキドキするはず
It should make your heart throb enough to melt
真っ白い煙ハイになれ
White smoke, let's get high
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない！
Not that kind of heart-throb!
けどまあ ある意味成功かな？
But well, in a sense, it's a success?
ラブは不用心 二強待ってなし感
Love is careless, a feeling of the top two not waiting
調合は試作中 今度のは飛び去る
The mixture is a prototype, this one will fly away
げっ、どこ行く！？ そんなトライ＆爆発を
Geh, where are you going!? Such trials and explosions
君と重ねていく 照れてて
Repeating them with you, being shy
キュンと覚めさせたくて ニア・ハズ
Wanting to wake you up with a throb, near hush
ラブに夢見る君が一番
The you who dreams of love is number one
追求、最高だらけっす
Pursuit, it's full of the best
爆発的なアンチドート
Explosive antidote
爆弾！ケミストリーダンス
Bomb! Chemistry dance
曖昧な君狂わすグラフィ
A graph that drives the ambiguous you crazy
平和な恋のジェネリック
Generic of a peaceful love
どんな毒も加速してさあ
Any poison accelerates, now
爆弾！君＋ハート
Bomb! You + Heart
溶けちゃってサンシャイン シナジー
Melt away, sunshine synergy
君こそが愛のアトミック
You are the atomic of love
もっと夢中になろうな
Let's become more obsessed
最！低！僕を食べて
Worst! Best! Eat me
キュンさせて留めたい君の胸
I want to make your heart throb and stay there
今まさに 幸福のラッシュ
Right now, a rush of happiness
爆弾！君と追加検証
Bomb! Additional verification with you
最！低！僕を食べて
Worst! Best! Eat me
ギュッとして僕の胸
Hold my chest tight
今まさに 幸福のラッシュ
Right now, a rush of happiness
爆弾！君とケミストリー
Bomb! Chemistry with you
究極は君とエターナリー
The ultimate is with you, eternally
君が好きってこの感情に 潰されてる
I'm being crushed by this feeling of liking you
足りないのはどちらの方か どうでもいいかも
Which one of us is lacking, maybe it doesn't matter
傷ついたって知らなよ ね 責任取ってよ
I don't care if I get hurt, hey, take responsibility
興味ないよ
作詞・作曲：jon-YAKITORY
I'm Not Interested
Lyrics/Composition: jon-YAKITORY
傷付いたって知らない様ね
You don't seem to notice even if I'm hurt
責任逃れ
Avoiding responsibility
「私はなんで好きなんだ？」って問い出す流れ
"Why do I like you?" The flow of questioning that
最低なあなたへ
To you, who's the worst
あの子のほうがいいんだもんね
Since that other girl is better for you
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested in you
マジ半端ないね
You're really half-hearted
舐めた真似
Such a sloppy imitation
ポップでキッチュなこの愛に
I hope I get destroyed by this
壊されりゃいい
Pop and kitschy love
ha-ha-ha-ha
止めないよ キミの愛を 独り占めしたい
I won't stop, I want to keep your love to myself
得だろうが 何だろうが 抱きしめてあげたい
Whatever the profit, I want to hold you
ライセンス契約 独占のフォールインラブ
A license agreement, an exclusive fall in love
逃がさない ずっと
I'll never let you go, forever
「キミが好き」って この感情に騙されてる
"I like you," I'm being deceived by this feeling
大事な方はキミかアタシか 決め兼ねてる
I can't decide if you or I am more important
バカすぎるキミへ
To you, who's too foolish
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested in you
ほら振り回して 好きなだけ
Look, keep me dangling as much as you like
ロックでビターなこの愛を
Because I won't give away...
渡さないから
...this rock and bitter love
バカだよね 色ボケだね
You're a fool, aren't you? Blinded by love
それ見たことか 片付かもう
See, I told you so! It's settled
もう他でもない
Now, it's nobody else...
あなたに呪われたまま
...but you, as I remain cursed
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested in you
バカなフリして あげただけ
I was just pretending to be a fool
愛と愛をぶつけ合って
Crashing our loves together...
ぐちゃぐちゃになって
...and getting all messy
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested in you
マジ半端ないね
You're really half-hearted
舐めた真似
Such a sloppy imitation
ポップでキッチュなこの愛に
I hope I get destroyed by this...
壊されりゃいい
...pop and kitschy love
ha-ha-ha-ha
見た目だけじゃワカラナイ
You can't tell just by looking
ワタシのこと可愛いだけと
You don't think I'm just cute...
まさか思っていないよね？
...do you?
ワタシの真実（ホント） 知っていてほしい
I want you to know my truth
予測誤差の範囲と 物理的自尊心も
Within the range of prediction error and self-esteem
厭わない オズモシスベースでいるけど
I don't mind, staying on an osmosis base...
心は常に青白く燃え
...but my heart is always burning pale blue
諦めはしない 媚びたりもしない
I won't give up, I won't flatter
私 おまけじゃない
I'm not just an extra
扱いにくい奴共の 甘く見ると
If you underestimate those difficult ones...
痛い目見るぞ
...you'll have a painful time
それでも 時には 逃げ出してしまいたい
Even so, sometimes I just want to run away
そんな衝動に 弱音吐き出す夜もある
There are nights when I let out my weaknesses
ほんの小さな 小さな妥協が
Just a tiny, tiny compromise...
積み重なり 重なって 動けない
...piling up until I can't move
大きな 大きな可能性を背負い
Carrying large, large possibilities on my back...
未来も狭めてしまうから
...because it will narrow the future too
どんなに苦しくても 辛くても
No matter how painful or hard it gets,
後悔だけはしない
I won't regret it
生き様を追い求めて 邪魔じゃなくて 生き方なんだ
Seeking my way of life, it's my way
現実との 距離を縮められたとしても
Even if the distance from reality is shortened...
オズモシスベースでいるだけ
...I'm just staying on an osmosis base
何事もなかったかのように
As if nothing happened
立ち止まりはしない 後戻りもしない
I won't stop, I won't go back
夢も捨てない
I won't throw away my dreams either
勝手な時 決めつけないで
Don't just decide when it's convenient for you
全部が私
It's all part of me
それでも
Even so,
時には温もりが恋しい
sometimes I miss the warmth
そんな感情に流されて
Swept away by those emotions,
迷う夜もある
there are nights when I get lost
こんな甘い甘い
Words so sweet, so sweet
言葉だけ求めてしまうような
that I find myself seeking only them—
弱さじゃない
it's not weakness
正解に大正解経て
Going through right and perfectly right answers,
私を強くしてくれたから
because they made me stronger
これが
This is...
これが私の
This is my...
ホント
truth
とても狭い狭い
From within a very narrow, narrow
世界の中から飛び出して笑うんだ
world, I'll leap out and laugh
広い広い
To the ends of the vast, vast
世界の果てまで駆け抜けて生きてくんだから
world, I'll keep running and living
どんなに泥臭く格好悪くても
No matter how unrefined or uncool it may be,
楽しんでやるさ
I'm going to enjoy it
イケてる面じゃめちゃくちゃじゃなくて
It's not about having a cool face or being a mess,
生き方なんだから
it's about how you live
アナスタシスガール feat. ラプラス・ダークネス
Anastasis Girl feat. Laplus Darkness
ハイ 注目！
Hey, attention!
あれもこれもそれもタブー
That, this, and that are all taboo
分かってんの？
Do you get it?
待って、ジョー
Wait, Joe
どーすんだバース ガチャガチャ口じゃませーそー
What are you doing, Verse? Clacking your mouth, shut up—
分かってんの？
Do you get it?
どーでもいいっしょ
It doesn't matter, does it?
豪快がベスティ狂死所キャパシティ
Dynamic is my bestie, a place of madness, capacity
ベイベー リズム負けしちゃいないしじゃない？
Baby, I haven't lost the rhythm, have I?
あげれば絶好調ミッドナイト
If I turn it up, I'm in top form at midnight
ドメンジョだけ追え 漂白してもねぇ
Just chase the surface, even if you bleach it
いタイの いタイの
It hurts, it hurts
飛んでいけないくらい
So much that I can't fly away
量産型も細胞で脳内宝集め出しましょう
Let's start gathering treasures in the brain with mass-produced cells
あたしアナスタシスガール
I'm Anastasis Girl
不滅強さがデキる
Immortal strength is possible
だ・か・ら La-La-La-La-La
So... La-La-La-La-La
いちにのさんでダン・ダン・ダン
One, two, three, and done-done-done
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
昨日イジメた罰
The punishment for yesterday's bullying
キミは La-La-La-La-La
You... La-La-La-La-La
地獄へダン・ダン・ダン
To hell, done-done-done
革命御来！
Revolution arrives!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
お口チャック
Zip your mouth
見慣れたハナ一文字
The familiar straight line of a nose
お口チャック
Zip your mouth
あたしだけに幸あれ
May happiness be mine alone
健やかなる時も病める時も
In health and in sickness
全肯定
Full affirmation
人間らしくあれ共
Be human-like together
美貌調節がふざけ
Fooling with beauty adjustment
代を 代を 代を 代を 代を
Generation, generation, generation...
代を 代を 代を ダイ！
Generation... DIE!
いタイの いタイの
It hurts, it hurts
飛んでいけないなら
If you can't fly away
やっちゃえ正常心で目には目を満たしてやりましょう
Go ahead, with a normal heart, let's satisfy an eye for an eye
あたしアナスタシスガール
I'm Anastasis Girl
ブレイクお通じ感
Break digestion sense
だ・か・ら La-La-La-La-La
So... La-La-La-La-La
いちにのさんでダン・ダン・ダン
One, two, three, and done-done-done
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
極めて遺憾です
It's extremely regrettable
キミは La-La-La-La-La
You... La-La-La-La-La
地獄へダン・ダン・ダン
To hell, done-done-done
革命御来！
Revolution arrives!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
Ah-ah-ah-ah
お願い 放っといてダイ
Please, let me be, DIE
Ah-ah-ah-ah
お願い 放っといてダイ
Please, let me be, DIE
あたしアナスタシスガール
I'm Anastasis Girl
不滅強さがデキる
Immortal strength is possible
だ・か・ら La-La-La-La-La
So... La-La-La-La-La
いちにのさんでダン・ダン・ダン
One, two, three, and done-done-done
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
昨日イジメた罰
The punishment for yesterday's bullying
キミは La-La-La-La-La
You... La-La-La-La-La
地獄へダン・ダン・ダン
To hell, done-done-done
革命御来！
Revolution arrives!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
すきじゃない！ すきじゃない！？ Ah!
I don't like you! I don't like you!? Ah!
ラブのリポート さめやらぬ感情
Love report, emotions that won't cool down
バカじゃないの 目を覚まして？
Aren't you an idiot? Wake up.
ねー 全然平常心で 興味と関心だらけ！
See? I'm perfectly calm, but full of interest and curiosity!
さらけ出して ウォンチュ
Lay it all bare, I want you
シカト出来なくて困る (無視すんなベイビー)
I'm in trouble because I can't ignore you (Don't ignore me, baby)
たまに構ってあげる (癖になっちまう)
I'll give you some attention sometimes (It becomes a habit)
絶妙な距離感 ゲーム
An exquisite sense of distance game
近く 近づく
Getting close, getting closer
一生 でかく でかく でかく でかく
Forever big, big, big, big
なんでもちょうだい 最大なスキ作りましょう
Give me anything, let's make a maximum 'love'
それがライクなのか ラブなのか
Whether that's 'like' or 'love'
はたまた両方なんでは！？
Or maybe both!?
なし あり なし 絶対あんだろ
No, yes, no, there definitely is
そして でかく でかく でかく でかく
And big, big, big, big
でかく でかく いや全部叶うからね
Big, big, no, it'll all come true
結局 おもい... おもい...
In the end, it's heavy... heavy...
なんかノらないわ！
I'm just not feeling it!
一旦一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's just try doing this together for now
Ah! あなたの スキは でかく スキデカく
Ah! Your 'love' is big, love-big
しばらくお付き合い よろしくなッ
Please bear with me for a while
スキ デカ スキ デカ...
Love-big, love-big...
ありがとうございます たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Thank you, tell everyone about all these emotions
俺だけに 見せてくれたっていいので
It's okay if you only show them to me
一人と特別 サービスできません！
I can't give special service to just one person!
それでもいいかな？
Is that still okay?
もっと知りたいことだらけ
Full of things I want to know more about
ほどほどにして でも知らない方が幸せか
Keep it moderate, or is it happier not to know?
どっちかにしてよね
Pick one already
絶妙な距離感 ゲームバランス取り合う
An exquisite sense of distance, matching game balance
一生 つかず 離れずは 辛いから ちょうどよく塩梅で
Because neither being together nor apart is painful, let's keep it just right
お互い もっと 分かり合えたら 特別になれる
If we can understand each other more, we can become special
そうだ いつも通じ合える
That's right, we can always connect
この先は 想像できないけど
I can't imagine what's ahead, but...
結構 いい時間も ギリギリでもいいから
Quite a good time, even if it's just barely
そのまま進みます オッケー
I'll keep going as I am, okay?
踏みつけていきましょう
Let's stomp forward
ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたい
I'd like to discuss our future here
もう話し合う必要ないでしょ
There's no need to discuss it anymore, right?
いいからほら
Just come on
3, 2, 1, Let's go!
一生 スレ違って 2人
Two people passing each other forever
一生 でかく でかく でかく でかく
Forever big, big, big, big
なんでもちょうだい 最大なスキ作りましょう
Give me anything, let's make a maximum 'love'
それがライクなのか ラブなのか
Whether that's 'like' or 'love'
はたまた両方なんでは！？
Or maybe both!?
なし あり なし 絶対あんだろ
No, yes, no, there definitely is
そして でかく でかく でかく でかく
And big, big, big, big
でかく でかく いや全部叶うからね
Big, big, no, it'll all come true
結局 おもい... おもい...
In the end, it's heavy... heavy...
なんかノらないわ！
I'm just not feeling it!
一旦一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's just try doing this together for now
一生 つかず 離れず 諦めず ちょうどよく塩梅で
Forever neither together nor apart, not giving up, let's keep it just right
お前と もっと くだらないことでも 笑っていたい
I want to laugh with you even over silly things
感情 突き合っていたい
I want to trade feelings with you
この先も 変わらない関係性を
Keeping a relationship that won't change from now on
ちょっと行き過ぎて またちょっと前進後退
Going a bit too far, then a bit of forward and backward
ひとまず進みます ラッキー
For now I'll go forward, lucky
そのまま戻ります なんでだよ
I'll go back as I am, why though?
スキは でかく スキ デカ しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Love is big, love-big, please bear with me for a while
不思議な関係 お見知りおきを
A mysterious relationship, nice to meet you
超常現象Tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走Timeless
Paranormal Tenderness, let's go east and west, Timeless
捨てろ劣等感 ほら最強じゃん 今 焼き付けろ
Throw away inferiority, see, we're the strongest! Burn it into your mind now
超常現象Tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走Timeless
Paranormal Tenderness, let's go east and west, Timeless
我等名探偵？！ いや迷探偵！ さぁ
Are we famous detectives?! No, stray detectives! Now...
Ba Ba Ba Ba Bang!!!
満月の夜潜り抜けて ビルの隙間でため息 Wow
Passing through the full moon night, a sigh in the gap between buildings, Wow
本性のルーペで探し出して 深い闇へ誘うの
Searching with the loupe of true nature, inviting into deep darkness
逮捕連行 秘密のShowtime 有言実行 世界を制圧
Arrest and escort, secret Showtime, action follows words, world conquest
オレンジに染まっていくホークアイ C'mon now
Turning into orange, Hawk Eye, C'mon now
君の為にMeLa MeLa 愛を燃やせ
For you, burn with MeLa MeLa love
MeLa MeLa 守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
MeLa MeLa since the day I vowed to protect it all
未来の為にMeLa MeLa この音にノッちゃえば
For the future, MeLa MeLa, just ride this sound
退屈なんて無縁でしょ サヨナラ
Boredom is irrelevant, isn't it? Goodbye
超常現象Tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走Timeless
Paranormal Tenderness, let's go east and west, Timeless
捨てろ劣等感 ほら最強じゃん 今 焼き付けろ
Throw away inferiority, see, we're the strongest! Burn it into your mind now
超常現象Tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走Timeless
Paranormal Tenderness, let's go east and west, Timeless
我等名探偵？！ いや迷探偵！ さぁ
Are we famous detectives?! No, stray detectives! Now...
Ba Ba Ba Ba Bang!!!
街灯が照らす欲望の影を 忍び足で欺いて Wow
Deceiving the shadows of desire lit by streetlights on tip-toe, Wow
震える手を握りしめよう 大丈夫 心配いらないわ
Let's squeeze those trembling hands, it's okay, no need to worry
変化カモフラージュ迷彩カメレオン
Transformation, camouflage, stealthy chameleon
中二病アイシャドウ甘いチョコレート
Chuunibyou eyeshadow, sweet chocolate
エッフェル塔段差を蹴るサイズ
Eiffel Tower size that kicks through the gaps
夢のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for our dreams
闇を燃やせメラメラ
Burn through the darkness, blazing hot
どんな時もこの声を届けたい
No matter when, I want this voice to reach you
崖っぷちでメラメラ
Blazing on the edge of a cliff
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up
恩返し 奇跡の おまじない
A miracle spell to return the favor
まさに見せ括弧 参勤交代 天然記念
A true display, a grand procession, a natural treasure
初陣意外 場外 だってお真面目
Unexpected debut, even out of bounds, so serious
どこにいたって迷子になってもバンプ
No matter where you are or if you're lost, just bump
有象無象でも無理巻いて
Winding through the masses, pushing ahead
電光石火 エスケープ
Lightning-fast escape
君のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for you
愛を燃やせメラメラ
Burn with love, blazing hot
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Since that day I vowed to protect everything
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for tomorrow
この音に乗ってメラメラ
Riding this sound, blazing hot
退屈なんて無縁でしょ さようなら
Boredom is a stranger to us, so farewell
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness
行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Let's go, running east and west, timeless
捨てろ劣等感 ほら最強じゃん
Discard your inferiority complex, look, we're the strongest
今 焼き付けろ
Burn it into your memory now
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness
行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Let's go, running east and west, timeless
我等名探偵？いや迷探偵
Are we great detectives? No, muddled detectives
さぁ ba-ba-ba-ba-bang
Now, ba-ba-ba-ba-bang
ねぇ、ねぇ、ねぇ、ルイさーん！
Hey, hey, hey, Lui-san!
めっちゃよかったね！
It was so good!
めっちゃよかった、めっちゃ楽しいね！
It was great, so much fun!
マジかっこいい！
That was seriously cool!
まだ終わってないから！これからも最高だよ！
It's not over yet! It's going to be the best from here!
なーにこれ？
What's this?
気づいちゃいました？待ってました！
Did you notice? I've been waiting for this!
これ変じゃない？めっちゃかっこいいじゃん、こよが作りました！
Isn't this weird? It's so cool, Koyori made it!
また経費使ったんか？
Did you use the budget again?
これがござるの給料８ヶ月分の…いやいやいや！
This is 8 months of my salary... No, no, no!
ということで、これは告知用カードを…
Anyway, these are announcement cards...
告知！ということでこの流れでね、グッズ紹介でございますね！
Announcement! So, moving on, it's time for merchandise introduction!
はい、ホロックス活動４周年記念グッズ！
Yes, holoX 4th Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
『Anniversary Parade』今日の18時より販売開始されております！
'Anniversary Parade' sales have started from 18:00 today!
プレミアムアクリル色紙！
Premium Acrylic Shikishi!
複製サインとロゴが箔押しになっててめっちゃいい感じ！
The replica signature and logo are foil-stamped, it looks great!
ホロカスリーブ！
Holocasu Sleeves!
こちらなんと60枚入り！
This one actually contains 60 sleeves!
アクリルスタンド！
Acrylic Stands!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、ぜひ！
The expressions are different from the key visual, so please check them out!
記念メダル！
Commemorative Medal!
ケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます！
It's a commemorative medal that comes with a case and a drawstring bag!
こちらね、期生ごとにデザインが異なっておりますので…
The design differs for each generation, so...
次のカードはなーにかな？オープン！
What's the next card? Open!
タイミーコラボ！
Timee Collaboration!
先日タイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど…
Regarding the rare part-time jobs we recruited for on Timee recently...
現地の様子があるということで、見てみましょう！
We have footage from the site, so let's take a look!
すごーい！ホロックスしてる！
Amazing! They're totally holoX!
ありがとみんな！他にもありますよ、ドン！
Thank you everyone! There's more, look!
なるようになるよ。
It'll be what it'll be.
でもこれで知ってくれた人もいるよね、多分。
But I'm sure some people found out about us through this.
ねえ！絶対そう！
Yeah! Definitely!
もう一枚あります！どうぞ！
We have one more! Here it is!
おおー！えっ、待って待って！
Oh! Wait, wait!
新宿！
Shinjuku!
アルペン東京だ！
It's Alpen Tokyo!
あれ、後ろにも映ってる！え、聞いてた？
Wait, we're on the screen behind them too! Did you hear about this?
聞いてた？あれ聞いてた？うそ、聞いてない！
Did you hear? Did you hear? No way, I didn't!
待って、今日のあの21時前に流れていたあのよくわからない映像。
Wait, that mysterious video that was playing before 9 PM today...
あのよくわからない映像…
That mysterious video...
おい！流れてしまったのかよ！大丈夫か？
Hey! It actually played?! Is it okay?
あれ流れてんのかよ！
That's what was playing?!
でももっとさ、なんかかっこいいMVとかさ、
But you know, I wanted something cooler, like an MV...
ライブ映像とか流したらもっと…
If they played live footage, it would be even...
なあ！？なんだよあれ！
Right?! What was that?!
でもありがとう！
But thank you!
ありがとー！やったー！
Thank you! Yay!
ということでこちら、応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
So, how many applications do you think we got for this?
300？
300?
でもさ、お仕事だからね。お仕事だから。
But you know, it's a job. It's work.
500人とか来てくれてる？
Maybe 500 people?
300人ぐらいじゃない？
Around 300?
大変だからね。
Because it's hard work.
なんと！
Well, actually!
数千人の応募が来たということでございます！
We received several thousand applications!
すごすぎる！ありがとう！
That's incredible! Thank you!
驚きすぎだろ！
You guys are overreacting!
えー！そんなに！？
What?! That many?!
全部給料もらったせいで。給料もらってるって決まってるから。
It's all because they're being paid. It's definitely because of the salary.
あの、いろはよりも多めに渡してます。
Um, I'm giving them more than Iroha's share.
やめてよ！しっかり福利厚生ホワイトな…
Stop it! We have solid welfare benefits, we're a "white" society...
アジトミーさんですから。
Because it's Ajitomy.
ありがとー。ありがとうございます。
Thank you. Thank you very much.
応募してくれたみんなもありがとう！
Thanks to everyone who applied too!
そして次はなんだ？
And what's next?
お、オープン！来い来い来い！
Oh, open! Come on, come on!
なにこれ？あ、来た！じゃじゃーん！
What's this? Oh, here it is! Ta-da!
タワーコラボだー！
It's a tower collaboration!
俺たちがタワーになるぞ！タワー！
We're going to become towers! Towers!
ということで、皆さんタワーコラボもう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
So, the information for the tower collab is already out, but here it is!
全国4ヶ所で行われる「holoX Tower Invasion」！
"HoloX Tower Invasion," held at 4 locations nationwide!
イェーイ！12月4日から開催されます！
Yay! It starts on December 4th!
さっぽろテレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力 MIRAI TOWER、梅田スカイビルで開催されますので、
It will be held at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Nagoya Mirai Tower, and Umeda Sky Building...
ぜひ、皆さん行ってくださいね！
So please, everyone, go check it out!
行ってねー！俺たちがホロックス重体タワー！
Go check it out! We are the HoloX Stacked Tower!
おい待て、待て！
Hey wait, wait!
今回大事なことがあるんですけど、ちゃんと予約をしないとですね、
There's something important this time. If you don't make a reservation...
あの、皆さん入れないんで。事前予約必須です。
Well, you won't be able to get in. Advance reservation is mandatory.
そうなんです、事前予約ね。忘れてる人も多分いると思うので。
That's right, advance reservation. I think some people might forget.
その場で行っても入れないらしい！
Apparently you can't get in if you just show up!
皆さん、予約を忘れないように！
Everyone, don't forget to reserve!
ぜひぜひお願いしますよ。
Please, please do it.
しとかないと。
Gotta do it.
おっと。次、次！
Oops. Next, next!
次！オープン！はい！
Next! Open! Yes!
えー、なんと！ホロライブの新サービス。
Um, what?! A new service from Hololive.
ライブの感動を最速でその手に！
Get the excitement of the live concert in your hands as quickly as possible!
おおー、すごい！どういうことだ？
Oh, cool! What does that mean?
秘密結社holoX、4周年のライブブロマイドが、
The 4th Anniversary Live Bromides for Secret Society holoX...
なんと今日のライブの写真が明日から、
Photos from today's live will be available starting tomorrow...
コンビニでプリントアウトできるんだ！
To be printed out at convenience stores!
どこでも手に入るんだ！
You can get them anywhere!
対象店舗はファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります！
Participating stores are FamilyMart, Lawson, and Ministop!
ありがとうございます！いっぱいある！
Thank you! There are so many!
そして今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです。
And apparently you can pre-purchase them online starting now.
マジ？！そうなんだ。
Really?! I see.
ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので、
But you can also buy them while choosing photos at convenience stores from tomorrow,
詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
So please check the link in the bottom left for details!
こっちこっち！このへん。
Over here, over here! Around here.
さらにですね、今回はそちらのお写真に、ブロマイドに、
Furthermore, this time, on those photos, on the bromides...
私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけれども。
It seems we can add our messages to them.
えっ、すごい！
Oh, wow!
あ、今から書く？
Ah, are we writing them now?
ちょっと、急すぎないか！？
Wait, isn't this too sudden?!
浮いてる、浮いてる！
They're floating! They're floating!
しかも何も考えてないけど、まあまあ考えて書いてください。
And I haven't thought of anything, but well, please think and write.
何にどうなんのこれ？考えて書いてください。
What is this going to be? Please think and write.
はい、えーっと。
Yes, uh...
時間もね、迫ってますから早く書いてください。
Time is running out, so please write quickly.
にゃにゃにゃ… さて。意外と集中力いるね。
Nya nya nya... Well then. This takes quite a bit of focus.
つなげ、つなげ。乾杯、乾杯で。できたー！
Keep it going, keep it going. Cheers, cheers. Done!
早いね！見せて！ちょっと待って。
That was fast! Show us! Wait a sec.
これ、あ、可愛い。まあまあこよりっぽいですね。
This, oh, cute. It's very Koyori-ish.
あーいいですね。こよりっぽい。いつまで書いてんねん。
Ah, it's good. Very Koyori. How long are you going to keep writing?
揚げにこだわった？回収回収。これ。
Obsessed with the deep-fry? Collect, collect. This.
サバンナ出して。皆さんお願いしますね。
Show the savannah. Everyone, please check it out.
ということでこれでお願いします。
So, please look forward to these.
まあ皆ね、何書いたかすごく気になると思うのですが。
I'm sure everyone is very curious about what we wrote.
こちらのメッセージの内容は、皆が… えっと、私が書いた…
The contents of these messages are what everyone... um, what I wrote...
おい！言っちゃダメですよ！
Hey! You can't say that!
言わないで！みんな買ってからの…
Don't say it! It's a surprise for after they buy it...
ダメに決まってんだろ。
Of course you can't say it.
ごめんなさい。はい、そして。
Sorry. Yes, and...
まだ2枚もあるんで。お次は、こちら！
There are still two more. Next is this!
な、なんと！「あの作品とコラボ！？」
W-what?! "Collaboration with THAT work!?"
え？！なに？なに？
Eh?! What? What?
あの作品？どれだ？これマジ知らない。
That work? Which one? I seriously don't know this.
あの作品って何ですか？こちらをどうぞ！
What is "that work"? Here it is!
サテー
Anyway...
突然デハアルガ、
It's sudden, but...
或ル秘密結社ノ
of a certain secret society...
話ヲシヨウ。
let's talk.
人間ハ、
Humans are...
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That mysterious group is...
偶像 ―― “アキドル” ナノダト云フ。
They say they are idols -- "Akidols".
ソシテ ――
And then --
正確ナ話ヲスルト、征服ショウトシテイルノハ
To be precise, what they are trying to conquer
エデンノ星ラシイ。
is apparently the Planet Eden.
タダ、ドイウコトカ、
However, for some reason,
交ハルハズノナキ世界ガ、
the worlds that were never meant to cross,
今回バカリハ 油断シテシマッタラシイ。
just for this once, seem to have let their guard down.
交
Cross
特別話 / 秘密結社holoX × 物語シリーズ 其ノ零
Special Story / Secret Society holoX x Monogatari Series Part 0
〈物語〉シリーズ × holoX コラボ開催決定
Monogatari Series x holoX Collaboration Confirmed
うわあああ！うそでしょ？！マジで？！
Whaaaa?! No way! Seriously?!
え、まずい、やばい！いいの？！
Wait, this is bad, this is crazy! Is this okay?!
めっちゃ大好きじゃんね！好き！やばすぎ！
We love it so much! I love it! This is too crazy!
どういうこと？！ありがとうございます！
What does this mean?! Thank you so much!
まじで？！怒られない我が輩？！
Seriously?! Will I not get scolded?!
怒られないよ！台本読んでないこと怒られるよ！
You won't! You'll get scolded for not reading the script!
物語シリーズとのコラボが決定しちゃいました！
The Monogatari Series collaboration has been decided!
どういうこと？！詳細は随時発表されるようです！
What is going on?! Details will be announced periodically!
お楽しみに！我々も分かっていない！
Look forward to it! Even we don't know!
え、どういうことですか？！
Eh, what does this mean?!
ちょっとうち等も焦ってるんですけど、最後に一つ！
We're a bit panicked, but there's one more thing!
もう一つ見ないといけないんで！一旦落ち着いて！
We have one more to see! Calm down for a second!
皆、この六つ目が何か、コメントで教えて！
Everyone, tell us in the comments what this sixth one is!
何かな？予想してみて！
What is it? Try to guess!
忍ちゃんコラボじゃないかな？！
Maybe a Shinobu-chan collaboration?!
最後の一つは何だと思いますか？
What do you think the last one is?
ヒントを言うと、今年二曲作りましたよね？
To give you a hint, we made two songs this year, right?
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
How many songs does holoX have in total?
何曲だっけ？えーと...
How many was it? Let's see...
たくさん！覚えてないのか？！
A lot! You don't remember?!
企画を除いて、全部で七曲あります！
Excluding projects, there are seven songs in total!
七曲！すごいね！
Seven songs! That's amazing!
ってことは？！皆分かってきたんじゃない？！
Which means...?! Everyone is starting to realize, right?!
気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、六枚目オープン！
It looks like some have noticed, so open the sixth card!
バン！ジャジャン！
Bam! Ta-da!
なんと！ファーストアルバムが出ます！
What! Our first album is coming out!
やったー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
ファーストアルバム「Secret ORDER」！
First Album: "Secret ORDER"!
混ざった、混ざった！Secret ORDERだよ！
I mixed it up! It's Secret ORDER!
holoXでの四年間をギュッと詰め込んだアルバムです！
It's an album packed with our four years in holoX!
「常夜リペイント」も新録アレンジ版を収録！
Includes a newly recorded arrangement of "Jouyari Paint"!
さらになんと未発表の楽曲も！
And what's more, there are unreleased tracks too!
え、8、9、10、11？！多すぎるー！
Wait, 8, 9, 10, 11?! That's so many!
通常盤なんですけど、上が見えない！早い！
Regarding the standard edition... I can't see the top! Too fast!
通常盤には初回限定特典があります！
The standard edition has a first-press limited bonus!
各メンバーのソロVer.ジャケットがランダムで封入！
Solo jackets for each member included at random!
四枚並べると一枚絵になるとのことですよ！
If you line up all four, they form a single picture!
ラプちゃんの角が刀の上に乗ってる！本当だ！
La+-chan's horn is on top of the sword! It's true!
これは並べないといけないね！
We definitely have to line them up!
完全生産限定盤の特典は...
The bonus for the Limited Complete Edition is...
holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが！秘密の仕掛け？！
a secret gimmick that fits holoX! A secret gimmick?!
我々も分かってない！この後22時から販売開始です！
Even we don't know! Sales start tonight at 22:00!
ぜひご予約お願いいたします！
Please make sure to pre-order!
告知盛りだくさんでしたね！告知カードはお役御免！
That was a lot of announcements! The cards are retiring now!
バイバーイ！消せるのこれ？！こよー！
Bye-bye! Can you make these disappear?! Koyo!
ここに予算かけすぎだろ！仕掛けやばい！
They spent too much budget on this! This gimmick is crazy!
holoXの力ってすげーんだから！
The power of holoX is incredible!
ライブもラストスパートでございます！
The live is now in its final stretch!
この後、何やらお楽しみ、サプライズがあるようです！
After this, it seems there's something to enjoy, a surprise!
最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いします！
Please stay tuned until the very end!
行くぞ皆！最後まで楽しんで！行くぞー！
Let's go, everyone! Enjoy until the end! Let's go!
S! S! S! S! S!
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
SSholoX! SSholoX!
「そこに跪け！」
"Kneel before me!"
「吐いて捨てるような現実を」
"Cut through this reality you'd spit out"
「一刀両断叩き斬る」
"Slashing through with a single stroke"
「終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ」
"Children who are lost in endless reincarnation"
「漆黒の翼で誘おう」
"Let's invite them with jet-black wings"
「我らエデンの星を統べる者」
"We are those who rule the star of Eden,"
「秘密結社・・・」
"Secret Society..."
「holoX！！」
"holoX!!"
「でござるでー！」
"de gozaru de!"
常夜リペイント
Joya Repaint
How Low？ どうしようもないこの世界
How Low? This world that can't be helped
（どうして欲しい？）
(What do you want?)
Black Out 終末告げる鐘が鳴る
Black Out, the bell announcing the end is ringing
「鳴らせ」
"Ring it"
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell announcing the end is ringing
ラッパッパッパラパって踊ろうぜ
Let's dance with a rappappappara-pa
Tripしようぜ陰キャも陽キャも Sing a Song
Introverts and extroverts alike, sing a song
気持ちいいことだけが すべて
Only the pleasant things... everything
落ちてゆく 闇の底へ
Falling down to the bottom of the darkness
甘い甘い メロディほら
Sweet, sweet melody, look
どうぞ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Come, come, towards the clapping hands
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained in darkness
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I'll give it all to you
常識 破り捨てろ
Discard common sense
くるくる狂い倒せ
Go round and round and crazy
火を付けろ
Set it on fire
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
悪のカリスマ
Charisma of evil
導くぞ民草
I'll lead the people
正義とか知らないし
I don't know about justice
地鳴らして誘い
Rumbling the ground and inviting
マジメに不真面目
Seriously unserious
弊社の通過儀礼
Our company's rite of passage
望み求め 願い叶え
Seeking desire, fulfilling wishes
世界征服
World conquest
ラーパッパって歌おうぜ
Let's sing with a rappappa
Swingしようぜ退屈な世界へ Bye Bye Bye
Let's swing and say bye-bye to this boring world
覚めることのない夢を
A dream you'll never wake up from
魅せる ほらお眠りなさい
I'll show you, look, please go to sleep
もっともっと 奥へほら
Look, further and further in
どうぞ どうぞ イキたいんでしょ？
Come, come, you want to go, don't you?
もうやめられない
I can't stop anymore
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're stained in evil
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望むもの与えよう すべて
I'll give you everything you desire
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules
くるくる回し尽くせ
Spin it all around
焼き尽くす
Burn it all down
すべてのマガイモノへ
To all the shams
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
「機は熟した！」
"The time is ripe!"
「狂気の宴の始まりだ！」
"The mad banquet begins!"
「貴様ら、準備はいいか！！」
"Are you all ready?!"
「お～～！！！」
"Ohhhh!!!"
「刮目せよ！！」
"Keep your eyes peeled!!"
(holoX! holoX!)
「手あげろ！手あげろ！！」
"Hands up! Hands up!!"
「叫ぶでござる～！」
"I'm shouting, de gozaru!"
「踊っちゃえ！踊っちゃえ！！」
"Just dance! Just dance!!"
「世界を手にするholoX！」
"holoX who'll take over the world!"
「世界を変えてくholoX！」
"holoX who'll change the world!"
「もっともっと！！」
"More, more!!"
「最後は全員いくぞ！」
"Everyone, one last time!"
(holoX！holoX！！)
(holoX! holoX!!)
「世界を手にするholoX！」
"holoX who'll take over the world!"
「世界を変えてくholoX！」
"holoX who'll change the world!"
「世界をこの手にholoX！」
"holoX with the world in our hands!"
心を 解き放て
Set your heart free
ほら どうぞ どうぞ
Look, please, please
身を任せて
Surrender yourself
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained in darkness
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I'll give it all to you
常識 破り捨てろ
Discard common sense
くるくる狂い倒せ
Go round and round and crazy
火を付けろ
Set it on fire
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
(holoX!)
Yes My Dark!
「我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社・・・」
"We are those who rule the star of Eden, Secret Society..."
「我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…」
"We who rule the stars of Eden, Secret Society..."
「holoX!!」
"holoX!!"
(で、ござる～!)
(De gozaru~!)
「機は熟した! 暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ、
"The time is ripe! Spirits from the dawn darkness,
準備はいいか!!」
are you ready!!"
「おー!」
"Oh!"
Are you ready?
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー (X!!!!)
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa (X!!!!)
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
When the night deepens, behold darkness.
能あるタカはPONで隠す
A clever hawk hides its talent with a 'PON'.
何に従え エゴイスト
Follow whatever you want, egoist.
ノートにニンニン サムライガール
Writing 'Ninnin' in the notebook, Samurai Girl.
やる気しないけど フルベッドでしょ チェキチェキ
Not feeling it, but going all in, right? Check-check!
征服すればおｋ 切り裂く赤字 ジャキンジャキン
Conquer and it's OK. Slashing red ink, Jakkin-jakkin!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
Makes you want to dance in the palm of evil.
ほら君 気付けば ノリノリです
Look, you're in the groove before you know it.
どうしようもない Don't, No Mine
There's nothing I can do. Don't, No Mine.
堕ちてく運命
Falling fate.
ならしょうがない
Then it can't be helped.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all.
Xと Xと Xと Xが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect in the middle,
Nextと Nextと Nextと Next 世界はもう 始まってる
Next and Next and Next and Next, the world has begun.
(ウオオオオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh)
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Fly, fly, towards where the darkness calls.
(ウオオオオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh)
アウンコクの エクスデス
Aun-un-koku-no-X-Death.
「混沌としたこの世界を 我らholoX色に 塗り替えるのだ!
"We will repaint this chaotic world into our color!
皆の者、かかれ!!」
Everyone, charge!!"
「Yes My Dark!!!」
"Yes My Dark!!!"
「完璧漆黒(アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ)!」
"Absolute Darkness Infinity!"
「エデンの星は我が手中に!」
"The stars of Eden are in my hands!"
「魔眼ホークアイ!」
"Evil Eye, Hawkeye!"
「お前もholoXの一員となるのだ!」
"You too shall become a member of holoX!"
「コヨリニュームビーム!!」
"Koyorium Beam!!"
「これで君も、コヨリメイトだ!」
"With this, you are now a Koyori-mate!"
「疾風木枯斬り!」
"Gale Withered-Tree Slash!"
「一刀両断、叩き切れ!」
"Cut them down in a single stroke!"
どうしようもない Don't, No Mine
There's nothing I can do. Don't, No Mine.
堕ちてく運命
Falling fate.
ならしょうがない
Then it can't be helped.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all.
刮目せよ!!
Behold!!
Xと Xと Xと Xが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect in the middle,
Nextと Nextと Nextと Next 世界はもう 始まってる
Next and Next and Next and Next, the world has begun.
(ウオオオオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh)
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Fly, fly, towards where the darkness calls.
(ウオオオオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh)
笑うのは holoXです
The ones who laugh are holoX.
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
(ウオオオオ!!)
(Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh!!)
機ハ熟シター
The time is ripe.
全テノ "holoXer" ヘ告グー
Announcing to all "holoXer"s.
集ヘ、決戦ノ地ー
Gather at the land of the final battle.
2026.4.29
PIA ARENA MM
秘密結社holoX 第一回全体ライブ「FIRST MISSION」開催決定!!
HoloX 1st All-Member Live "FIRST MISSION" confirmed!!
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
Are you ready to take the world?
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
The beginning of the mad banquet.
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
#SSholoXWorldRepaintProject
やったー！すげぇー！信じられない！
We did it! This is amazing! I can't believe it!
Takane Lui: 皆も驚いてくれてる！やったー！
Takane Lui: Everyone is surprised too! We did it!
Hakui Koyori: いかがでしたかー！？
Hakui Koyori: How was it?!
Takane Lui: ヤバいね！
Takane Lui: This is crazy!
Takane Lui: まだ早いからね！ヤバいねー！
Takane Lui: It's still early though! So crazy!
La+ Darknesss: ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
La+ Darknesss: And so, our in-person live concert has finally been decided!
Takane Lui: ありがとうございます！やったー！
Takane Lui: Thank you very much! We did it!
Takane Lui: 「FIRST MISSION」や！PIA ARENA MM！
Takane Lui: It's "FIRST MISSION"! At PIA ARENA MM!
Takane Lui: ということで皆それぞれね、感想と...
Takane Lui: So, I'd like each of you to share your thoughts...
Takane Lui: ライブに向けた抱負をお願いしたいと思います。
Takane Lui: ...and your aspirations for the live concert.
ん〜、まずは、じゃあ私から。
Hmm, first, well, from me.
はい！
Yes!
はい。ん〜。決まったな！
Alright. Hmm. It's decided!
はい！ここから、決まったな。決まったね。
Yes! From here, it's decided. It's decided, right?
いや〜めちゃくちゃね、あの、デビューの時から
Wow, really, you know, since our debut...
ライブやりたいねって、言ってて。デビュー前から。
We've been saying we want to do a live.
デビュー前から。それが、もうありがたいことに
Even before our debut. And now, thankfully...
皆の協力のおかげで
Thanks to everyone's cooperation,
ホロクサーさんたちの応援のおかげで
Thanks to the support of the Holoxers,
叶いました！やったー！
It came true! Yay!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you very much!
えー、もう…ふぅ。ホロクスの
Uh, already... whew. holoX's...
皆で、当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので
We all want to make it exciting on that day,
ぜひ皆遊びに来てください！かっこいいホロクスを見に来てね！
So please come and visit us! Come see the cool holoX!
ということで、続いては、じゃあこよ！
With that said, next is... well, Koyo!
はい！
Yes!
えー、今言ってた通り皆ライブやりたいねって話もしてたし
Uh, like you just said, we were talking about wanting to do a live,
やっぱこよは一番忘れられない風景が
And for Koyo, the most unforgettable sight is...
初めてのフェスで、ホロクスで、やった時の
When we performed as holoX at our first fes,
あの、常夜リペイントで、会場がもう、わーってなってくれたのを浴びた時
Bathed in the crowd going wild during "Tokoyo Repaint"...
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで、やっぱりその、今度はね、
I can never forget that, so this time,
ホロクサーさんたちだけの、会場、俺たちの会場で、
A venue just for Holoxers, our own venue...
やれるわけじゃないですか。俺たちの箱で！
We get to do it there, right? In our own venue!
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！そして、
I'm so incredibly happy! And...
できて、本当に、この…やらせてくれることに、してくれた大人の皆さんにも！
And for making this possible, for the adults who let us do this!
大人の皆さん！ありがとうございます！
To the adults! Thank you very much!
それで、この4人のできる力をすべて出して、そして歌とダンスもね、
So, we'll give it everything we've got, for the singing and dancing too,
より一層、力を込めて、やって、いきますので！
We'll put even more effort into it!
絶対、現地、そして現地来れない人は映像でも、絶対見に来てください。
Please come to the venue, or if you can't, watch the stream!
ろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
お願いします！ナイス！
Thank you! Nice!
はい！さかち！
Okay! Sakachi!
はい！みんな！
Yes! Everyone!
生で俺たちの声が聴ける機会！
A chance to hear our voices live!
ホロクスのこのハーモニーが聴ける機会！
A chance to hear this holoX harmony!
うるさいけど！雄叫び！俺たちの共鳴！共鳴が聴ける機会！
It's loud, but! The roar! Our resonance! A chance to hear it!
来たぞ！
It's here!
皆さん！いやもう本当にね、ホロクス、やっぱみんな言ってるけどデビュー前からね、
Everyone! No, really, as everyone's saying, since before our debut...
現地ライブを、このメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので、
We've always said we wanted to do a live with these members,
それがやっと叶ってね、デカい声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのを、
And that's finally coming true, getting excited together...
今か今かとね、楽しみに、しております！
We're eagerly looking forward to it!
我々もね、4人とも、しっかり当日まで、レッスンや、
We too, all four of us, will work hard until the day of, with lessons...
練習も含めパフォーマンスも、全部色々、皆に楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて、
Including practice, performance, thinking of ways for you to enjoy,
挑みますので！ん！
We'll take on this challenge!
見ている皆さんも！ぜひ！全力で！楽しみにして！そして当日は楽しんでください！
Everyone watching too! Please! Look forward to it with all your might!
頑張ります！盛り上げる準備、できてます！
We'll do our best! We're ready to pump things up!
できてるぞー！イエーイ！
We're ready! Yay!
じゃあ最後、総帥、総帥決めてくれ！
Now finally, Leader, Leader, wrap it up!
お願いします！
Please!
いやちょっ、毎回この最後やめてほしいんだよね。しょうがないよね。
Hey wait, I wish you'd stop making me go last every time. Oh well.
ちょっと、みんな、ついに…
Listen, everyone, finally...
ホロクスが、
holoX...
俺たちが、
We...
ライブーーー！
LIVE---!
もうみんなはさ、もうすごいライブやりたい、音楽大好き、みたいな、
You guys always said you really wanted to do a live, that you love music...
ずっと聞いてたからさ、
I've been hearing it all this time,
俺は嬉しいよ！
I'm happy!
いやもう、当事者だよ、当事者！私も…やっぱりライブがね、一番楽しいから。
I'm one of you, one of you! For me... after all, lives are the most fun.
皆さんもやってる、
You guys too,
やっぱホロクスの活動って、なんかライブって感じじゃじゃん？
holoX's activities feel like they're meant for lives, right?
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかも
So, that we can do it with just us, and...
ホロクサーがばーって、いるところでできるのが、嬉しいよな！
In a place packed with Holoxers... that makes me happy!
嬉しいよー！熱いな！
We're happy! This is hot!
いやもう俺たち、色々あったけど、
No, we've been through a lot, but...
これからも、本当に、4人いれば大丈夫だから。頑張ろう！
From now on, really, as long as the four of us are together, it'll be fine.
一致団結！頑張るぞー！
Unity! Let's do our best!
ありがとう！速報です！
Thank you! We have breaking news!
はい！
Yes!
トレンド1位ということで！ありがとうございます！
We're #1 on trending! Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ここから4月29日まで、もう止まらねぇぞ、イベントに出まくっててください！
Until April 29th, we won't stop! Keep coming to our events!
はい！
Yes!
ということで改めて、秘密結社holoXファーストライブ『FIRST MISSION』は、4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
Once again, holoX's first live, 'FIRST MISSION,' will be on April 29th at Pia Arena MM!
空けとけ！空けとけ！空けておいて！
Clear your schedules! Keep the date open!
諸々の詳細は、後日発表予定とのことなので、皆さん続報を待てでござる！
Details will be announced later, so wait for further news!
ろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
そして、そして、先ほど聴いていただきました新曲、『暁光エックス』です！
And, and, the new song you just heard, 'Gyoko X'!
はい、聴いていただきましたけれども、このあと
Yes, you heard it, but after this...
MVが公開となります！
The MV will be released!
22時10分よりですね、MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
At 22:10, we'll be premiering the music video!
やったー！ / おおー！ / エクスデスだ！
Yay! / Ooh! / It's Xdeath!
おしゃれですね。かっこいい。
It's so stylish. And cool.
そして本日24時、12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので...
Also, the digital release starts today at 24:00—that's 0:00 on December 2nd...
ライブに向けてたくさん聴いてくれよな！
So please listen to it a lot in preparation for the live!
いや、もうコールできるところいっぱいだからね！
Yeah, there are so many parts where you can join in the calls!
めちゃくちゃもう、ライブのための曲だから！
It's totally a song made for live performances!
エクスデス！エクスデス！
Xdeath! Xdeath!
お前ら新曲いっぱい聴いて、予習して、ライブ楽しみに待っててほしい！
I want you guys to listen to the new song a lot, study up, and look forward to the live!
そしてアルバム『SecretORDER』を持って...
And take the 'SecretORDER' album...
持って？ / 持って！ / 忘れないように気をつけてね！
Take it? / Take it! / Make sure you don't forget it!
ライブ来てね！ / 運ばなきゃ！
Come to the live! / We have to carry it!
聴いて予習してね！ / はい！
Listen and study up! / Yes!
アルバムは22時から販売開始です！もう1分ないで！
The album goes on sale at 22:00! There's less than a minute left!
早い！みんな買ってね！
So fast! Everyone, please buy it!
ホロックスのみんな、本当に4年間ありがとな！
Everyone in holoX, thank you so much for these four years!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
来年はもうホロックスの、我々の年にしていくので！
Next year, we're going to make it holoX's year!
そうだね！ / 頑張ろうね！
That's right! / Let's do our best!
5年目もよろしくお願いします！
Please support us in our fifth year too!
じゃあみんな、せーので行くよ！せーの、バイバーイ！
Alright everyone, on three! One, two... Bye-bye!
改革！改革！改革！改革！
Revolution! Revolution! Revolution! Revolution!
Ladies and gentlemen, introducing...
Six... five... four... three... two... one...
Let's go!